wholelifechallenge.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy - Whole Life Challenge

**Whole Life Challenge Privacy Policy**

Whole Life Challenge, Inc. respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the Personal Information (defined below) that you may provide us while using this Site (as defined below). We currently operate the website wholelifechallenge.com, including all of its subsites (typically any web pages that include wholelifechallenge.com as the URL, such as [www.wholelifechallenge.com/the-7-daily-habits/](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/the-7-daily-habits/)) and all software, applications, products, features and services made available, displayed or offered by or through our web site or subsites (collectively, the “ **Site** ”). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the [Terms of Use](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/terms-of-use/) (the “ **[Terms of Use](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/terms-of-use/)** ”), which governs your use of this Site in general. This Site is published and maintained by or on behalf of Whole Life Challenge, Inc., with offices located at, 929 Colorado Avenue, #117, Santa Monica, CA 90401 (“ **WLC** ”).

WLC may be referred to in this Privacy Policy as “we,” “us,” “our,” or other similar pronouns.  Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/terms-of-use/).

**Purpose**

Your privacy is a serious matter to us.  We are committed to respecting the privacy rights of our Site visitors and users.  In order to make your visits to our Site and use of the services available through our Site as worthwhile as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information and we may collect certain information automatically from your computer or mobile device when you visit us or use certain features on the Site. “ **Personal Information** ” means information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, and includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone, wireless and/or fax number; short message service or text message address or other wireless device address; instant messaging address; demographic information (such as gender, age or nationality); personal health information, body, fitness and lifestyle measurements, self-assessments, before and after pictures, workout results; vital records; exercise, diet and hydration habits; and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual as well as other information that is associated with you and your use of the Site. This privacy statement explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected on our Site, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy so that you understand how WLC treats your information.

**What and Who This Applies To**

This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** “), which applies only to information collected via the Site, governs your use of WLC’s Site, including: (a) what types of information we collect about you when you use the Site; (b) how the information will be used or disclosed; (c) your rights with respect to our collection and use of your data; (d) to whom we disclose the information; and (e) how we safeguard the information. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to entities that WLC does not own or control, such as third party advertisers, partners, sponsors, licensors, licensees, vendors and service providers. We are not responsible for the information practices of any of these or other third party sites, advertisements, offers, content or links that may appear on our Site.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, other than through our Site, such as by phone, through postal mail, in-person such as at events and challenges and through other live and print media.  You may obtain copies of our privacy policies applicable to information collected other than through our Site, by sending us a request in writing that specifies how and when your information was provided to us.

This Web Site is intended for users who are located in the United States of America and Canada. This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States. The Site is a social fitness website.  We believe that your sharing of your challenge information, whether participating in a challenge as an individual or as part of a team, and the accountability that comes from sharing your challenge information with others, are important elements to helping realize the benefits of a challenge and taking steps to improve your health and wellness.  By providing Personal Information or other information to use through the Site, or otherwise accessing or using the Site, you agree to our privacy practices outlined here.  If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy or our [Terms of Use](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/terms-of-use/), please do not use the Site.

**What Information is Collected on this Site?**

**User-Provided Information**

**_General_**

We collect Personal Information from users of our Site, for example, through such users’ submissions, registration for and player participation in challenges, transactions and completion of online forms on our Site. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts or features on our Site, sign up for, participate in or upload or submit information or data to us in connection with a challenge or event, interact or communicate with team members or others in challenges or events, enter sweepstakes and contests, complete surveys, use software, social media channels and platforms, applications or tools made available to you by or on behalf of us, post reflections, contribute to your daily score, a chat room, message board, comment section, list serve, blog, vlog, wiki, or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Site, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on our Site, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Site. We also collect information regarding your participation, fitness, sleep, nutrition, hydration, lifestyle, health and results from our challenges, events and programs, such as the Whole Life Challenge and any application, social media platform, web pages or tools made available to you to track, log, collect or display data or information related to a challenge and your health, fitness, lifestyle, nutrition and diet.  

You may be able to send information from our Site to your friends and family members through our Site by clicking on an “E-mail to Friend”, sharing tools, purchasing a gift certificate to be delivered via email, creating and inviting others to participate on a challenge team, or similar button on our Site or in an e-mail that we have sent you.  In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us.  Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**_Personal Health Information_**

The Site may, from time to time, ask users to provide certain personal health information, and we will collect this data, which includes (for example) health conditions, exercise habits, workout results, body measurements, vital records, sleep, diet, hydration and nutritional data, body type, and other characteristics. This information is optional for the user to provide but some of this information, such as sleep, diet, hydration, nutritional and workout information, may be required for players to participate in a challenge in order to track their progress and check their individual and/or team status on the leaderboard. WLC will use this information to operate challenges, including contributing to the leaderboard, and to help create a better experience and fitness and health program to provide to its users, including as part of a challenge.  For example, it may monitor the demographics, fitness characteristics, and location of participants in an event or challenge sponsored, operated or organized by WLC, and WLC may use that information to understand where demand for certain services are to best utilize its resources to provide them. In addition, WLC may publish some of your personal health information in connection with your Site account or challenge or event registration and participation (with team members and generally with other participants) such as with a given challenge and may share some of your personal health information with its service providers or other third parties in connection with operation of the Site. To protect your privacy, if WLC shares your personal health information with one of our service providers, such service provider will be required to agree to and comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Unless we have your prior written consent to do otherwise, if WLC shares your personal health information with a third party other than one described in the preceding sentence, we will only do so in a way that anonymizes your Personal Information, including your personal health information, and aggregates it with other users’ Personal Information.

**Site Usage Information**

**_Cookies_**

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you.  Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive or otherwise persist on your system or device. They are used to make WLC’s Site easier to use, to make its advertising better, and to protect both you and WLC.  Cookies track where you travel on our Site and what you look at and purchase. They may store your username and/or password.  A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Site to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Site.

Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Site or certain areas or features of the Site.  The following web sites provide information on how to adjust the cookies settings on some popular browsers:

You can also use a browser plug-in such as [Ghostery](https://www.ghostery.com/)* from Ghostery, Inc. (A browser plug-in is a piece of software which adds extra capabilities to your browser—for example, to play video or scan for viruses.). 

**_Interest-Based Advertising_**

We and third parties, including service providers, may engage in interest-based advertising to deliver advertisements and personalized content that we and other advertisers believe will be of interest to you. To the extent third party vendors are using cookies to perform these services for us or others, we do not control the use of this technology or the resulting information, and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Ads may be delivered to you based on your online or mobile behavior (on our Site and non-WLC sites), your search activity, your responses to one of our advertisements or e-mails, the pages you visit, your general geographic location, or other information. These ads may appear on our Site or on third party web sites. The service providers with whom we work to help us conduct interest-based advertising may be members of self-regulatory associations such as the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)](http://www.aboutads.info/).  You may also see advertisements for third parties on our Site or other web sites or properties, based on your visits to, and activities on, our Site and other sites.

To find out more about interest-based advertising, your choices or to opt out of the use of cookies to tailor content or advertising to you, you can visit these sites: [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  Note that if you choose to opt out, you won’t necessarily see fewer ads.  However, the ads you see may be less relevant to your interests.

**_Clear GIFs_**

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “ **Web beacons** ” or “ **pixel tags** ”) or similar technologies, in the Site and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

**_IP Address and Clickstream Data_**

Our server automatically collects data about your server’s Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. When you request pages from our Site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Site; the Web site you visit after this Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers.  We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information, but will not share such information, when linked with your Personal Information, with a third party without your prior consent.

**_Your Use of Our Apps_**

When you download and use one of our applications, we and our service providers may track and collect app usage data, such as the date and time the app on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been downloaded to the app based on your device number.  App-related tracking technologies in connection with non-browser usage (e.g., most functionality of a mobile app) can only be disabled by uninstalling the app. To uninstall an app, follow the instructions from your operating system or device manufacturer.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Site usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers.

**Right to Opt In and Opt Out**

You have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal

Information, including by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by submitting a request in writing to Whole Life Challenge, Inc., 929 Colorado Avenue, #117, Santa Monica, CA 90401, Attn: Privacy Officer. At the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Site, you will have the opportunity to elect to, or not to: (1) receive correspondence from us, or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes.  You may also make this request by sending an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).   Users may opt not to receive our electronic newsletters or those of third parties when providing Personal Information. Users who opt in may remove themselves from mailing lists at any time through the My Profile pages or by following the instructions at the end of the e-mail they received from us.  If you opt not to provide certain Personal Information when registering for or using our Site, however, you may not be able to use some of our services such as participating in a challenge or using message boards.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and

communications with us.  Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will

not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your

Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

**How is the Personal Information used?**

We will use the Personal Information you provide to our Site in connection with the services and features we provide to you through our Site. For example, such information may be necessary to register you for a challenge, events and newsletters, update your status as part of a challenge, respond to your requests and messages, provide you with news, challenge or event information and other offerings, for feedback purposes, and for marketing and promotional purposes.  We may also use your Personal Information for internal record keeping, to analyze and track user progress through our challenges and fitness programs and events, and compare you to other persons or users of the Site or other websites, software, applications or tools in various ways.

We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Site usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. Also, advertisements and other content displayed to you on the Site may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your Personal Information and Site usage information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.  In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, challenges and events, sponsored, developed, organized or operated by us and others, that we think might interest you.   **You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above.**

We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Site and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

**Do we share Personal Information and Site Usage information with others?**

**Public Forums**

When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Site, such as a message board, chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, vlog, wiki or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Site, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public.   Such information may, for example, be accessed by everyone on the internet, be indexed by third party search engines, and be imported, exported, distributed, and redistributed by us and others without privacy limitations and once published or displayed may be impossible to remove. Such information may be associated with you by such outside parties based on what you provide or disclose.

For these reasons, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information, including your home address, phone number, other information that would enable other users to locate you, or financial information, on these areas of our Site. If you do not consent to displaying your personal information such as your full name in connection with participation in a challenge, please do not participate in the challenge.  To request removal of your Personal Information from a public forum or other public area of our Site, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1c75727a735c6b7473707970757a797f747d707079727b79327f7371).

**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**

WLC does not currently respond to “Do Not Track” requests. A uniform standard has not yet been adopted to determine how DNT requests should be interpreted and what actions should be taken by websites and third parties. However, you may opt-out of tracking on this website by changing your browser settings.  See our cookies policies above for instructions.

**Event and Challenge Participation**

When you register for or participate in a challenge, or submit scores, results, feedback, posts or information for any of our challenges, events, or other activities, your submissions, records and results are kept by WLC and may be made available to other challenge participants.   When you register for or participate in a challenge, certain information will be available to other participants in the challenge, including your full name, team name and profile picture.  When you join a team as part of a challenge, certain information will be visible to your team members, including, without limitation, reflection posts and other posts you make, scoring submissions,  workouts, sleep, hydration and nutrition information, progress you make in the challenge, leaderboard placement and daily entries related to the challenge.  You also have the option of making certain information, including Personal Information, available to challenge participants, such as email address, birthday, ‘about me’ information, before and after photos, body measurements, reflections and workout results.  These records and media are used to determine and track your participation in a challenge or event, performance, eligibility for prizes, and placement, leaderboard status, and team status and profiles, among other things. Additionally, the Site may use this information in various other ways, such as data analysis, communicating results news via different media, social media or websites, promotional use, or other general public information purposes, through various media, means and methods that currently exist or that may be developed in the future. For a more detailed description of the terms and conditions on which your submissions, records and results may be used by WLC, please see the [Terms of Use](https://www.wholelifechallenge.com/terms-of-use/). 

**Third-Party Offers**

We may provide visitors and participants an opportunity to receive offers from other entities who have services, products and offers that we think might be of interest to you.   **Unless you elect not to receive such offers by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above, we may from time to time provide your Personal Information to these entities so that they may send you these offers.**  If you change your mind and no longer want us to share your Personal Information with these types of third parties, follow the instructions to opt out in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above.

**Co-sponsored Events, Contests, Sweepstakes and Offerings**

Some of our challenges, events, content, programs, contests, sweepstakes and other offerings may be co-sponsored by another company or companies. In those situations, the information we obtain from you in connection with such contest, sweepstakes or offering may be shared with our co-sponsor(s), unless you instruct us not to by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information.

**Payments**

When you make any payments, deposits, or other transactions, we will share transaction information with only those third parties necessary to complete the transaction. We will require those third parties to agree to respect the privacy of your information.

**Service Providers**

We may use third-party partners to help operate our Site, collect and analyze data and information, host, operate or support software, applications and tools and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our subsidiaries, entities owned, related to or controlled by us, service providers and other third parties that provide software, products or services for or through this Site or for our business (such as Web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, message board and customer support service providers, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). This is intended to help improve or promote our services provided. If you would like additional information on the policies we enforce with respect to our service providers, please contact us as described below.

**Aggregate Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior and health, fitness, workout and nutrition data as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Site and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

**Legally Compelled Disclosures**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas.  We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. If we are required or compelled to disclose your user information by a government authority, we may attempt to notify you of such disclosure if we are permitted to do so by law.

**Business Transfer**

In the event that WLC, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, operation of law, change of control, consolidation or liquidation, your Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets. The terms of this privacy policy will continue to apply to your Personal Information that is transferred to the new entity

**Third-Party Ad Servers**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site.  If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available in the FAQ section of wholelifechallenge.com. These companies may use information (generally not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide

advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your Personal Information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer Web site at [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Wireless Addresses**

If the e-mail address you provide to us is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive

messages at such address from WLC and the rest of the third parties with which we share your e-mail address ( **unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above** ). You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

**Short Message Service**

We may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless

device via short message service (“ **SMS Service** ”). If you subscribe to one of our SMS Services, you thereby agree to receive SMS Service messages at the address you provide for such

purposes.  Such messages may come from WLC and/or the rest of the third parties with which we share your address (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above).

You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device you use to sign up for the SMS Service, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. To use the SMS Service, you must be 18 years of age or older and reside in the United States. You must first register and provide all required Personal Information, which may include, for example, your name, SMS address, wireless carrier and, if fees are applicable to the SMS Service you subscribe to, billing information (either your credit card information or mobile service carrier information if applicable fees will be billed through your carrier). We may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks.  We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of

the SMS Service. We may also access the content of your account and/or wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and/or service- related complaints.

By signing up for the SMS Service, you consent to receiving, from time to time, further messages which may include news, promotions and offers from us, our subsidiaries, entities owned, related to or controlled by us and partners, and you consent to our sharing of your Personal Information with such parties for such purposes, unless and until you have opted out of these activities by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above. Please follow the instructions provided to you by third parties to unsubscribe from their messages.

**Your Access Rights**

You may review, correct or change the Personal Information that is stored in your user account

on this Site by visiting the My Profile area of your account on this Site.

You may send us new or updated information at any time by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will endeavor to respond to your request to access, update or delete your information, including your user account, as soon as practicable. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.  

**California Privacy Rights**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code section 1798.83 permits WLC customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding WLC’s disclosure within the immediately preceding calendar year of that California resident’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, contact our support staff through the following link:  [WLC Contact Customer Care](https://wholelifechallenge.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new).   If you would like to change your current account preferences, go to the My Profile section of your WLC account.

**Security**

WLC will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal

Information provided to this Site. We require a personal username (log-in name) and a password in order for users to access their Personal Information. We restrict access to personal information to WLC employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf.

**Inherent Risks**

No security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.  

If you contact us by e-mail or a “contact us” or similar feature on our Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

You may be able to create an account on our Site with a username and password, for example, to participate in the Whole Life Challenge or other features. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Site by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify WLC of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session.  It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify WLC when you desire to cancel your account on this Site. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as 

possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

**Phishing**

With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send e-mail messages to consumers, purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, requesting that the consumer provide personal, often

sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail

appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the web site requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity has come to be known as “phishing.”

If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your Site password or credit card information) via e-mail or to a

web site that does not seem to be affiliated with our Site, or that otherwise seems suspicious

to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#85ecebe3eac5f2edeae9e0e9ece3e0e6ede4e9e9e0ebe2e0abe6eae8).

**Consent to Processing Information for Persons Outside the United States**

The Site is operated and controlled by us from the United States. Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than your country.

**Third-Party “Linked-To” Web Sites**

When you are on our Site you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not

operated by WLC, including other web sites operated by unrelated third parties. These sites may collect Personal Information about you. WLC does not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other web sites, and applies solely to information collected by WLC on this Site.  

**Children Under Age 13**

We are a general audience site, and do not knowingly request Personal Information from anyone

under 13 years of age. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use our Site, including by attempting to post on any message board, participate in blogs, discussions and chat rooms, register for any challenges or events, or otherwise provide any information to the Site. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. No information collected from children is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside of any WLC challenge. 

We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the internet and we encourage

parents to teach their children about safe internet practices. Parents may wish to consult the resources on children’s privacy and safe internet practices that are available through the Federal Trade Commission.  We also strongly suggest that you have installed and use “Parental Controls” for your web browser.

We take seriously our obligation to safeguard the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information collected from our users, and have established and will maintain procedures that are designed for that purpose. Children and parents should be aware, however, that no

system is completely secure from hackers, network failure and error, and we cannot guarantee the confidentiality, security and integrity of information maintained on our service. Please see the section entitled “ **Security** ” elsewhere in this Privacy Policy for further details.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

WLC reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or

practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Site to sending you an e-mail.  When we change this Privacy Policy in a material manner, we will update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4c25222a230c3b2423202920252a292f242d202029222b29622f2321) or through:

Whole Life Challenge, Inc.

929 Colorado Avenue, #117

Santa Monica, CA 90401

**Last Modified Date of this Privacy Policy: April 4, 2017.**
